Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, March 1974-July 1974 (Box-folder 18/34)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, October 1974-April 1975 (Box-folder 18/35)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, July 1975-October 1975 (Box-folder 18/36)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, January 1976 (Box-folder 18/37)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, June 1976 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, July 1977 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, April 1979 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, July 1979 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, November 1979 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Quarterly Reports, March 1980 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Court Papers, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Court Papers, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Court Papers, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Subject Series: EEOC Compliance, 1977 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Subject Series: Ironworkers vs. Herrick Corp. (Hayward, CA), 1975 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Subject Series: Plasterers and Cement Masons, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - United Construction Workers Association vs. Peter Brennan, 1974 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Center vs. Local 86: Subject Series: United States vs. Ironworkers Local 86 Title VII, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - United States Department of Labor Manual: Contract Compliance in Construction, 1976 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - United States Department of Labor: Operations Manual, 1976 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Sybil Brown v. Puget Sound Electrical Apprenticeship & Training Trust, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 19/17)
    - John G. Yates, Apprenticeship Agreement, 1973 (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings II, File 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings II, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings III, File 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings III, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings III, File 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings III, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers Pleading File IV, File 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers Pleading File IV, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings IV, File 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings IV, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings V, File 1 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings V, File 2 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers Pleading, File VI, Long List of Local 7 applicants in 1975, 1976 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings VI, 1976 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings VII, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings VIII, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleading File VIII, Part 1, 1977 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleading File VIII, Part 2, 1977 (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings IX, Mail Affidavits, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings IX, Apprenticeship Applications, Part 1, 1978 (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings IX, Apprenticeship Applications, Part 2, 1978 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings X, 1978 (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings X, Evidence, 1978 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XI, Part 1, 1978 (Box-folder 20/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XI, Part 2, 1978 (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XI, Notice of Removal of Restricted Materials, Subpoenas, 1978 (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XII, Part 1, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XII, Part 2, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XII, 1979 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XIII, Subpoenas to Testify, Part 1, 1979 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pleadings XIII, Subpoenas to Testify, Part 2, 1979 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Pretrial Order- Final, 1979 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, O-CF Appeals File, 1978 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, O-CF Appeals File, 1978 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7, International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, First Interrogation to Local 7 and Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC), 1974 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation's (OCF) Second Interrogatories to Plaintiffs, 1977 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation's (OCF) First Interrogatories to Plaintiffs, Notice of Removal of Restricted materials, 1975 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Local 7 First Interrogatories, Notice of Removal of Restricted materials, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Answers to Interrogatories, Apprenticeship Applications, 1975 (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 Interrogatories, 1976 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC) Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Answers to Interrogatories, 1975 (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Local 7 First Interrogatories- Defendant with Answers, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings I, Part 1 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings I, Part 2 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings I, Interrogatories, Part 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings I, Interrogatories, Part 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings II, Part 1 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Yates v. Asbestos Workers Pleadings II, Part 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Back Pay Claims- Originals From Clerk's Office, 1980 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Back Pay Claims, 1980 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Back Pay Claims- Originals From Clerk's Office, 1980 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Litigation Expenses--Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Back Pay Claims, 1980 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Proposed Pretrial Orders, 1979 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Exhibit List, 1979 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Louis Meschke, 1979 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Jose Aguilar, 1979 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Mario Peter Scontrino Testimony, 1979 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Mario Peter Scontrino Testimony, 1979 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Chuck Flint Deposition & Exhibits, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Reyes Mirabal, 1979 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Emily Van Bronkhorst, 1977 (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Walter Strigen, 1976 (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Thompson, Donald, 1976 (Box-folder 22/19)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Bertram J. Molker, 1976 (Box-folder 22/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Planichich, John, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Mike McGinness, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Ken McCaffree, 1976 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Exhibits to McCaffree Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 22/24)
    - Yates v. Metalclad Insulation, Pleadings I, 1979 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Yates v. Metalclad Insulation, Pleading II, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Yates v. Metaclad Insulation, Pleading II, 1979 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Yates v. Metalclad, Dispatch List, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Jerrold Sproat., 1976 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Michael Strigen, US entry papers, 1976 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Western Insulation Contractors Association (WICA) Deposition, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ken McCaffree, 1979 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Deposition of Harold Stenberg, 1976 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al. John Ashley Deposition, 1979 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ben Bradley, 1979 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al. Deposition of Ed Lontz, All Hiring Hall Lists, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al. Deposition of Edward Lontz, 1979 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Roy Tonneson, 1979 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of David L. Wells, 1976 (Box-folder 23/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of David Wells, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 23/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Joseph Williams, 1977 (Box-folder 23/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Michael McGinnis, 1979 (Box-folder 23/18)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Michael McGinnis, 1979 (Box-folder 23/19)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Gregory Buford, 1979 (Box-folder 23/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Gregory Buford, 1979 (Box-folder 23/21)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Axel L. Peterson, 1976 (Box-folder 23/22)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits to Peterson Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 23/23)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Billy Philley, 1975 (Box-folder 23/24)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Terry Philley, 1975 (Box-folder 23/25)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ed Lontz, 1976 (Box-folder 23/26)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ed Lontz, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 23/27)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of John Yates, 1979 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of John Yates, 1979 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of John Yates, 1979 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Bill Bartlet, 1979 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Bill Bartlet, 1979 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ted Dana, 1979 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ted Dana, 1979 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits of the Deposition of Gary King, 1969 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits to Boscovich Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits to Gary King Deposition, 1972 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Gary King Deposition, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of George Boscovitch, 1976 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Douglas Lavan, 1976 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Wesley Chase, 1976 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of James Chew, 1976 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Carvel del Fierro-Witness File, 1979 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Fred George, 1977 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Richard Keely, 1979 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits to Richard Keely Deposition, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Glen Blakely, 1979 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Ronald Price, 1979 (Box-folder 24/21)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of Harley Bird, 1979 (Box-folder 24/22)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Deposition of William C. Blair, 1976 (Box-folder 24/23)
    - Local 7 Pretrial Order, 1977 (Box-folder 24/24)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Exhibits, Harley Bird Deposition, 1979 (Box-folder 24/25)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Michael Mack- Witness File, 1979 (Box-folder 24/26)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Materials Produced by Joint Apprenticeship Committee (JAC), 1979- (Box-folder 24/27)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Class Member Mailing, 1978 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Apprenticeship Mailing List, 1978 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Local 7 Address Search, 1977 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Western Insulation Contractors Association (WICA) Affirmative Action Documents, 1978 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Manuel Rodriguez- Witness File, 1977 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Search for Potential Class Members, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Miscellaneous Trial Exhibits, Member lists, Charts, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Affirmative Action File II, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Consent Decree, 1972 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Brand-Parsons Notices, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Gregory Buford- Witness File, 1979 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Documents Produced by Local 7, Deposition of Edward T Lontz, Wages and Working Conditions, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Chuck Luck Deposition, 1973 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Documents Produced By Local 7, Rodriguez File, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., MC Caffree Negotiating Notes, 1979 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., Updating Pretrial Order, 1972 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., O-CF Dispatches, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Yates v. Local 7 International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers et al., O-CF Appeal- Working File, 1977 (Box-folder 25/18)